audiob.us 2019-08-24

# Audiobus: Live, app-to-app audio.

## Privacy Policy

**Last updated 13 Jun 2019**

This Privacy Policy describes how and when we (Audiobus Pty Ltd) use and share your information when you use our products.

### Information we collect

#### Device information

We may collect device-specific information, such as your hardware model and operating system version.

#### Application information

We may collect information about your installation, such as the application version number.

#### Information you give us

When you contact us, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing.

The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to use our forum to provide a username and email address. We collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfil the purpose of the visitor's interaction with us. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies on our forum to help identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Information we share

We do not share or disclose your private personal information unless necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request.

We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as aggregate usage statistics.

## Opting Out

You can configure your browser to prevent your computer from storing and sending us cookies. [Here are ways to disable cookies](https://www.wikihow.com/Disable-Cookies). 

* * *

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice. If you have any questions feel free to contact us directly at [privacy@audiob.us](mailto:privacy@audiob.us)
